{
    "subject": "resource/Slovakia",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Bratislava",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Slovakia is Bratislava.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8500012755393982,
            "question": "What is the capital of Slovakia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8136764764785767,
            "question": "What is the history of Bratislava as a capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6558934450149536,
            "question": "Is Bratislava a major city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6303415298461914,
            "question": "Where is Bratislava located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5131973028182983,
            "question": "What are some notable landmarks in Bratislava?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4011957347393036,
            "question": "How would you describe the architecture of Bratislava?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36555489897727966,
            "question": "What are some cultural events held in Bratislava?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28918778896331787,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist attractions in Bratislava?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2474992871284485,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Bratislava?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20973750948905945,
            "question": "What language is spoken primarily in Bratislava?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Slovakia is Bratislava.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8790_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Bratislava?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8790_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist attractions in Bratislava?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8790_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some cultural events held in Bratislava?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8790_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8790_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the triple \"The capital of Slovakia is Bratislava\" is supported by the context information. This can be confirmed from documents with file paths starting with \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8790/re-ranker-msmarco/\" (i.e., 39.txt, 51.txt, 60.txt, 71.txt), which all mention Bratislava as the capital of Slovakia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the documents provided do support the statement \"The capital of Slovakia is Bratislava,\" as multiple documents explicitly mention this fact."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}